https://www.esoftech.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy The following is a description of how we handle information we may learn from your use of our site.Information you may provide through visiting our site falls into one of two categories: personal information and aggregate information. Any personal information (for example, your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) you transmit to the site by electronic mail or otherwise will be used by eSoft for the purpose for which you have provided it. Aggregate information is information that does not identify you, and may include, for example, statistical information concerning the web pages on our site that users most frequent. We collect aggregate information for system administration, to measure the number of visitors to our site, to improve site performance, and to help us make the site more useful. Any other communication or material you transmit to the site, such as questions, comments, suggestions or the like, will be treated as non-confidential.eSoft will not collect any personal information about you through our web site unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it to us.We have in place security control systems designed to prevent the unauthorized disclosure of your personal information. Due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot provide assurances as to the security of your personal information, and eSoft expressly disclaims any such obligations.
Submit Your Application Note: Max. accepted file size is 3MB. Supported file types: doc, docx,pdf Submit Application
×
